hi assalamualaikum Hamid whatever but everywhere
I am sitting shared a bit about mine okay I am
from the a19 button okay today I would like to
tell you about deaf injury do you know about
life insurance okay if you don't know it's
okay I let me explain this it to you life
insurance is a contract between initial and a
policyholder English with no insurance payment
of a death benefit to main beneficiary when
the issue that the insurance company promised
a disability in exchange or premium pet fight
the policyholder today I will share a bit of
you about further and share via stand up
overhead do you know what is this mean to
you Prudential plc is an Israeli portfolio of
business focused on structure growth market the
business had individual to do it via life and
in with the arpita's financial person - Lila
and health insurance and retirement and
asset management solutions I choose GRU
the interim plan pervert Inc that is it then
we take the illness and permanent disability
they're a few of benefit when you choose PR you
review plain first you'll get a long cover second
you also get a photo birth premium you can get
both the option another benefit you also get a
lump sum increase in monthly income and we do
them at the top then excursion that I choose
implant in the piece Prudential shall not pay
the death benefit pursuant to country section
a of the master policy if the death of the
insured remember is to preserve within the
first year from the cover them shown in
the insurance certificate accordingly the
Progressive Insurance in the issue a certificate
will be found with the interest to the insured
member so test i'm from me i hope you can get
a little knowledge about prudential interim
policy thank you for your listening if you
want more information about us to contact
us at our website or just call us indirect
prudential always listening always understanding